<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ZimMall</string>
    <string name="signature">©SekaiStudios2020</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">ActivityHome</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="about_us">Zimbabwean Mall is not a new idea, rather a bespoke one.
    There are thousands of online stores out there but because of our country\'s statue and economic
    situation, sadly we never used to have a reliable online solution for shopping... Until now.
    With Zim Mall, the possibilites Open up, wether you are a Shopper or Seller, you get the best of
    of the best of service.</string>

    <string name="out_partners">We take Pride in our Philosophy of Work which encompasses a great
    deal of team work. We have worked from the very beginning to build a network of partners that
    we can rely on for the services we provide. Our First partner, Sekai Studios handles Technological devs to keep
    us up-to-date with the trends in Tech and maintain the Security of servers back to back.

    Secondly, Our main supplier for products is Afia Leigh Pvt(Ltd) who run a shipping business across the World.
    Afia have some of the best products at the lowest price possible, it is rather evident in our catalogs.
    This service hinges on great Delivery services, which admittedly are always improving, but, we would
    like to thank Swift for the delivery services they offer to get your products to you so we never miss a
    deadline.

    The circle if not complete is the last partner isn\'t accounted for and that You! Zim Mall aims to serve
    the people, hence we can\'t be efficient unless we give you the chance to really participate. Therefore
    as a user, you can buy of sell products on our App for close to nothing. </string>

    <string name="concl">This is not the full summary of who we are, please visit sekai.co.zw to get a
    full picture. Follow our Social Media pages to get updates on new products, new app updates and other
    valuable information like Job Vacancies at Zim Mall. Thanks for the time, happy shopping.</string>
</resources>
